{
    "subject": "resource/The_Mating_Call",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "resource/Silent_film",
    "human_readable": "The Mating Call is a silent film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9852891564369202,
            "question": "Is 'The Mating Call' a silent film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7184010744094849,
            "question": "What type of film is 'The Mating Call'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5657063126564026,
            "question": "Who directed 'The Mating Call'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4909852147102356,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'The Mating Call'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42369693517684937,
            "question": "Where was 'The Mating Call' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36453568935394287,
            "question": "What genre is 'The Mating Call'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31454214453697205,
            "question": "Were there any sound effects in 'The Mating Call'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2865145802497864,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in 'The Mating Call'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27437278628349304,
            "question": "Was 'The Mating Call' a commercial success?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2696056663990021,
            "question": "When was 'The Mating Call' released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Mating Call is a silent film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4687_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was 'The Mating Call' a commercial success?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4687_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in 'The Mating Call'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4687_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any sound effects in 'The Mating Call'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4687_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4687_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4687_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4687_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4687_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4687_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4687_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4687_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4687_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4687_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4687_55.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents multiple times mention that \"The Mating Call\" (1928) is a silent film, supporting the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}